여보셔
나는 이사를 가니까
이제부턴 네가 집세를 내야 돼
I'm moving out, so you're
in charge of paying the rent.
알았어, 언제 내는데?
-When's it due?
-On the first.
- 매달 1일이야
- 달마다 낸다고?
And that's every month?
No, just the months
you want to live here.
아니, 네가 여기서
살고 싶은 달만 내
이건 전화요금 고지서
Okay, here's the phone bill.
Oh, my God!
엄마야!
That's our phone number.
그건 우리 전화번호야
I know I kind of sprung this
me-moving-out-on-you thing.
내가 너무 갑작스럽게
나가는 건 사실이니까
-Why don't I cover you for a while?
-No way!
당분간은 내가 부담할게
안 돼, 그럴 순 없지
Joey Tribbiani does not
take charity...
조이 트리비아니는
동정을 거부한다
anymore.
앞으로는
-It's not charity, Joe.
-Forget it.
- 동정이 아냐
- 글쎄 됐다니까
고맙긴 하지만
이제 네 돈은 안 받겠어
Thanks, but I'm done
taking money from you.
I can take care of myself.
What's next? Come on.
내 일은 내가 알아서 해
또 뭐가 있어, 내놔 봐
좋아, 이건 전기요금
Here's the electric bill.
-This is how much we pay for electric?
-Well, yeah.
전기요금이 이렇게 많이 나와?
그래
So we'll do
the rest of the bills later, then?
다른 고지서는
나중에 봐야겠네?
The One On The Last Night
Will Joey have to give up
the apartment?
그래서 조이가
아파트를 포기한다고?
그럼 안 되는데
굳이 돈을 안 받겠다잖아
I offered him money,
but he wouldn't take it.
How much does he need?
얼마나 있어야 되는데?
1,500달러면 몇 달은
버틸 것 같지만
$1500 would cover him
for a few months...
but I have to trick him into
taking it so I don't hurt his pride.
녀석 자존심을
상하지 않게 줘야 돼
Why don't you hire him as an actor?
걔를 배우로 고용해라
You could have him dress up
and put on skits whenever you want.
옷 입혀서 연극을 시켜
네가 원하는 건 뭐든지
Well, that would help the pride thing.
그럼 자존심 팍팍 살겠다
얘들아
그래, 와! 정말 예쁘다
내일부터 나랑 동거할까요?
Wow, you look great! Do you wanna
move in with me tomorrow?
- 좋아
- 좋지?
여성동지들은 오늘 뭘 하나?
Any plans for tonight?
아쉽지만 레이첼이랑
마지막 밤이니까
Instead of being sad on my
last night with Rachel...
we're going out to celebrate
Rachel's moving in with Phoebe.
피비 집에 들어가는 거
축하할 겸 저녁 먹으려고
그리고 내 생일이거든
-And also my birthday.
-It's not your birthday.
네 생일 아냐
What a mean thing to say! I'd never
tell you it wasn't your birthday.
정말 너무한다, 난 네 생일
아니라고 한 적 없어
얘들아
어서 와
You guys have anything planned
for the big last night?
남자들은 마지막 밤에
뭐할 생각인데?
놀러 나가느니
그냥 아무 것도 안 하려고
Instead of just hanging out,
we figure we'd do nothing.
오늘 닉스 시즌 첫 경기잖아
Knicks' season opener tonight.
I thought you'd come and watch it.
우리 집에 가서 TV나 보자
글쎄다, 로스
I don't know, Ross.
Not if you talk about how you gave up
basketball to become a paleontologist.
고생물학자 되려고 농구인생
포기한 인간이 하나 있어서
정말로 고생물학자가 되려고
농구인생을 포기했단 말이야
I did give up a career in basketball
to become a paleontologist!
- 피비, 저기...
- 아직 옷 안 입었어?
-Phoebe..
-You're not dressed yet?
We're supposed to start having fun
in 15 minutes!
15분 후에 나가 놀 거야!
And clearly, not a minute sooner.
정확히 그렇게 되겠지?
레이첼, 짐은 다 쌌겠지?
제발 짐은 쌌다고 말해 줘
You are packed, though, right?
Please tell me you're packed?
물론 다 쌌어
모니카, 진정해
Of course I'm packed.
Monica, relax.
I wanted to ask Phoebe
what I should wear.
피비한테 무슨 옷을 입을지
물어보려고 한 거야
My God, I can't get a minute of peace.
숨 돌릴 틈도 없이 불러대네
Oh, my God!
엄마야!
모니카한테 너 죽는다
Monica's just gonna kill you.
I know.
나도 알아
죽으려면 그 옷이 좋겠다
What you're wearing is fine
for that.
레이첼, 혹시...
You're not packed!
짐 안 쌌어?
You're not packed even a little bit!
한 개도 안 쌌잖아
놀랐지!
Surprise!
뭐?
Don't get mad,
because this is what happened.
화내지 말고 내 얘기 들어봐
짐을 싸다 이런 생각이 든 거야
I started packing,
then I realized, "What am I doing?"
'내가 뭐하고 있지?
난 짐 엄청 못 싸는데'
I am lousy at packing, right?
맞지?
But you love packing!
넌 짐 싸는 거 좋아하잖아
So as a gift to you
on our last night....
마지막 날에
네게 주는 선물이야
짜잔
I'll be coordinator!
그럼 난 코디네이터다!
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
I didn't get you anything.
난 아무 것도 없는데
미안해서 어떡하니
Everybody has to help.
Phoebe, can you help?
그럼 다같이 하자
피비, 너도 도울 거지?
난 약속이 있어
I have plans.
-You have plans with us.
-That's right.
우리랑 약속했잖아
맞아
좋아
Chandler can make boxes, Ross can
wrap and Joey can lift.
챈들러가 박스를 만들고
오빠는 포장하고
조이는 나르는 거야
남자들한테 도와달라고 해
Tell the guys
they have to help out.
- 알았어
- 그래
My God, thank you!
진짜 고마워
Monica's gonna make you pack!
She's got jobs for everyone!
빨리, 모니카가 너희들
짐 싸는 데 동원할 거야
Now, it's too late for me,
but save yourselves!
난 이미 늦었지만
너희들은 달아나
잘 들어
11시간 후에 이삿짐센터에서
올 텐데 레이첼은 짐을 안 쌌어
The movers will be here in 11 hours.
Rachel hasn't packed.
Now, everybody has to help.
Chandler..
모두 도와줘
- 챈들러는 먼저...
- 난 조이랑 약속이 있어
I have plans with Joey.
-You said you were doing nothing.
-Yes, but for the last time.
아무 것도 안 한다면서
하지만 마지막 기회잖아
그럼 좋아, 오빠는...
Fine. Now, Ross..
-I can't do it.
-Why not?
나도 안 돼
왜 안 돼?
-Don't you have Ben?
-Because I have Ben!
벤이 온다면서
왜냐면 벤이 올 거니까
It's almost past his bedtime.
Where is he?
8시면 벤은 잘 시간인데
지금 어디 있어?
디너파티에
He's at a dinner party.
He's really coming?
I can see in your apartment.
정말로 오는 거야?
오빠 집 여기서 다 보여
당연히 오지
Of course he is. What?
일하기 싫어서 아들을
이용한단 말이야?
You think I'd use my son as an excuse?
What kind of father do you think I am?
내가 그런 아빠로 보여?
All right. Sorry.
알았어, 미안해
I gotta go make a fake Ben.
가서 가짜 벤을 만들어야겠다
Here it is.
대령이오
Our last pizzas together as roommates.
룸메이트로서 같이 먹는
마지막 피자야
이거 사올 줄 모르고
중화요리 시켰는데
I wish I knew that.
I ordered Chinese.
그것도 괜찮지
Well, that's okay.
야, 사실 어떤 면에선
더 잘 어울리는 걸?
In a way it's kind of nice.
You know?
최후의 만찬이니까
Our last dinner together. Me,
bringing the food of my ancestors...
난 내 조상의 음식을 주문하고
you, the food of yours!
넌 너희 조상 걸 주문하고
I had an idea for what to do
on our last night.
우리의 마지막 밤을
기념하는 의미에서
What do you say we play a little
foosball for money?
돈 걸고 푸스볼 게임 어때?
Are you crazy? You haven't beaten me
since my injury-plagued '97 season.
미쳤냐?
나 다쳤던 97년 말고는
네가 이긴 적이 없잖아
-It'd be easier to give me your money.
-Yes, it would.
그냥 돈을 주는 게 낫겠다
물론 그렇지
What do you say to $50?
50달러 어떠냐
I say to it:
"50 dollars, you are more than I have."
어디 보자, 50달러야
넌 나보다 부자구나
If you know that you'll win,
what difference does it make?
어차피 네가 이길 건데
무슨 상관이야
-You're on.
-Okay, let's play.
- 좋아, 하자
- 그래, 시작한다
빅게임이야
이탈리아 대...
The big game. Italy versus...
China, apparently.
중국이겠지, 아마도
이 롤러블레이드 좀 봐
Look, it's the Rollerblades.
세상에
Oh, God!
You remember when we got these?
이거 샀을 때 기억나?
아니
넌 거기 없었구나
I guess you weren't there.
기분 처지게 왜 이래
You guys,
we said we were gonna have fun.
얘들아, 그때 생각나?
Come on. Hey, remember the time....
You don't remember?
생각 안 나?
Sorry, Phoebe. I'm just really sad
that I'm leaving.
미안해, 막상 떠난다고
생각하니 너무 슬프다
I'm gonna miss you so much.
많이 보고 싶을 거야
This doesn't have to be so sad,
though, you know?
그렇게 슬픈 일만도 아냐
Instead of thinking about
how you'll miss each other...
서로 그리워할 걸 생각지 말고
그립지 않을 일들을 생각해봐
you should think of the things
you're not gonna miss.
I don't think there's anything.
그런 건 없는데?
Come on, there's gotta be something.
왜 이래, 뭔가 있을 거야
아니, 얘는 완벽해
She's perfect.
난 하나 있어
I have one.
좋아, 그럼 너 먼저 얘기해
Okay, you can go first.
이건 그립지 않을 거야
I guess I'm not gonna miss the fact...
that you're never allowed
to move the phone pen.
전화기 옆 펜을
못 옮기게 한 거
그거 좋다 얘
That's a good one.
Okay, Monica, anything?
그럼 모니카는 어때?
레이첼이 펜을 옮긴 거?
You know,
does Rachel move the phone pen?
Sometimes.
가끔은 그랬지
Always, actually.
실은 맨날 그랬어
자, 그럼 됐네
기분이 나아졌지?
There you go.
Doesn't everyone feel better?
Not just the phone pen.
펜만이 아냐
I never get my messages.
한 번도 메시지를
전해준 적이 없어
You get your messages.
전해줬잖아
It doesn't count if you have to
read them off your hand...
네가 소파에서 잠들었을 때
손바닥에 적힌 메모를 본 거?
after you've fallen asleep
on the couch.
그래서 누구 메시지를
못 받았는데? 챈들러?
So you missed a message from who?
Chandler?
Or your mom?
아님 엄마?
Or Chandler?
아님 챈들러?
아님 엄마?
Or your mom?
It worked! No one's sad!
정말 제대로 됐네
아무도 안 슬프지?
그렇지!
I win again!
또 이겼다
That's, like, 500 bucks
you owe me!
이제 너 500달러 빚졌어
Man! Five hundred dollars.
좋았어, 500달러면
전기 팍팍 써도 되겠다
That is a lot of electricity, huh?
I gotta buy some food.
먹을 거부터 사야겠네
Give me a chance to win my money back.
Sudden death...
한 번만 만회할 기회를 줘
단판 승부로
한 골에 1,000달러
one goal, $1000.
- 진짜야?
- 물론
-You serious?
-Yes!
좋아
Get ready to owe me.
- 또 잃을 준비나 해
- 알았어
Here we go. Ready?
그럼 간다, 됐어?
- 저런, 저런, 저런...
No...
경사가 있나
one can beat me!
That's why only the little fake men
are supposed to do the kicking.
그니까 우리 선수들만
발길질을 하는 거야
여보세요?
Hi, Ross.
See, other people call me!
그래, 오빠
봐, 다른 사람도 전화하지?
Oh, your brother. Score!
누구? 너희 오빠?
잘 빠졌수!
What's up?
왜 그래?
방금 벤이랑 들어왔어
인사하려고
I'm here with Ben.
Thought we'd say hi.
벤 바꿔 줘
-Put him on.
-Ben, say hi to Aunt Monica.
벤, 고모한테 인사해라
지금은 말하기 싫은가 봐
I guess he doesn't feel like
talking right now.
He's smiling, though.
그래도 웃고 있어
Okay, talk to you later.
알았다, 나중에 걸게
아빤 농구선수 될 뻔했단다
You know, Daddy was gonna be
a basketball player.
너희들 우울할 때가 더 낫다
I think it was better
when you guys were sad.
이 롤러블레이드 생각나?
Hey, remember the Rollerblades?
You know what else I won't miss?
"I'm Monica.
보기 싫은 건 또 있지
'전 모니카예요, 변기를 하루에
17번 닦죠, 사람이 앉아있어도'
I wash the toilets 17 times a day,
even if people are on it!"
"Hi, I'm Rachel.
Is my sweater too tight?
'난 레이첼이에요
스웨터 딱 붙었나요?'
'아녜요? 그럼 빨아서
줄여야겠네요'
I'd better wash it and shrink it!"
"I'm Monica. I never get messages
from interesting people."
'난 모니카예요, 따분한
사람만 나한테 전화하죠'
야, 나도 전화해
I call her.
'세상에, 로스를 사랑해
미워해, 사랑해, 미워해'
"Oh, my God! I love Ross. I hate
Ross. I love Ross. I hate Ross!"
"My God!
I can't find a boyfriend.
'맙소사, 애인이 없잖아'
I'll stumble across the hall and sleep
with the first guy I find there!"
'복도 건너가서 처음 만난
남자랑 잘 거야'
너희들 왜 이래
오늘이 마지막 밤이야
You guys, come on,
this is the last night!
그래, 네 말이 맞다
마지막으로 부탁하자
Yeah, you're right, and so for the last time
I would like to ask you:
얼레리꼴레리
내 방에서 나가!
Boo-hoo. Get out of my room!
We should get a move on if we want
to make those dinner reservations.
저녁 예약시간에 맞추려면
빨리 해야겠다
Still broken?
여전히 작동불능이냐?
It sucks, man.
돌겠다
너와의 마지막 밤에 인생에서
가장 중요한 두 가지를 잃다니
Your last night, and I lose the two
most important things:
The foosball table...
푸스볼 테이블...
그리고 500달러
and $500.
There are other ways to win back
your money. How about blackjack?
돈을 되찾을 방법이 있을 거야
블랙잭은 어때?
Not my game.
그건 별로야
You know what?
We can play a new game.
좋아, 그렇다면...
새로운 게임을 하자
-It's fun!
-What's it called?
이건 재미있어
이름이 뭔데?
Cups.
'컵스'
-I don't know how.
-I'll teach you. It's easy and fun.
- 컵스는 할 줄 몰라
- 가르쳐줄게
이리 와, 정말 쉽고 재미있어
-All right.
-Here you go.
- 알았어
- 자, 돌린다
I have two queens.
What do you have?
난 퀸이 두 장, 넌 뭐지?
-A 2 and a 5.
-You win! Fifty dollars!
2랑 5
네가 이겼다, 50달러
-Really?
-Let's play again.
- 정말?
- 그럼, 다시 해보자
-What have you got?
-4 and a 9.
이번엔 뭐야?
4하고 9
You're kidding, right?
농담 아니지?
-No. Why?
-That's a full cup!
- 그래, 왜?
- 그건 '풀 컵'이야
Damn, I am good at Cups!
나 컵스 진짜 잘한다
I'm not talking to her.
쟤랑 말도 하기 싫어
하지만 네가 먼저
사과를 해야지
You have to take the first step...
because she's the one who's
leaving. It's harder for her.
떠나는 쪽은 레이첼이고
그것만으로도 힘들잖아
Maybe you're right.
네 말이 맞다
But she made fun of my phone pen!
내 펜을 비웃었단 말이야
I know. I took it hard too.
내가 봐도 그건 좀 심했어
She's in there right now, crying.
I can hear her.
여기서도 우는 소리가 들린다
울긴 뭘 울어
She's not crying.
슬픔을 삼키고 있다니
정말 당찬 애야, 들어가
She's holding it in.
She's so brave. Go.
I feel bad about what happened..
저기, 레이첼
아까는 미안했어
뭐하는 거야?
-What are you doing?
-I'm unpacking.
- 짐 풀고 있다
- 뭐?
방 안 뺄 거야
I'm not moving.
Is that picture straight?
제대로 걸렸니?
왼쪽으로 20블록 더 가야 돼
It needs to go about 20 blocks
to the left.
뭘 착각하나 본데 챈들러랑
살겠다고 나선 건 바로 너야
You're the one who wants this
big change and to move in with Chandler!
You should go!
Why do I have to leave?
그럼 네가 나가야지
왜 내가 나가?
- 여긴 내 아파트야
- 내 집이기도 해
-It's my apartment!
-It's mine too! What else you got?
다른 건 없어?
이건 어때?
네가 나가!
How about: You're moving!
알았어, 모니카
됐어, 진정해
This is ridiculous.
정말 웃기는 짓이다
네 짐을 싸야지!
We should be packing you!
-Hey, how you guys doing?
-Great. Monica's moving.
잘 돼가니?
그럼, 모니카가 나간대
I am not!
난 안 나가
그럼 왜 네 물건이
이 박스 안에 있지?
Really? How come all your
stuff is in this box?
얘들아, 이게 무슨 일인지
대충 알 만하다
Okay, you guys,
I think I know what's going on here!
얘들아, 스톱!
You guys? Stop!
I know you're acting mad because
it'll make it easier to leave.
그렇게 서로 화난 척하면
헤어지기가 좀 수월하겠지만
But deep down, you're really sad.
Deep, deep down.
마음속 깊은 곳에선
정말 슬퍼하고 있잖아
아냐, 난 화났어
-No, Phoebe, I am mad!
-Well, deep down!
- 아주 깊은 심연
- 역시 화났어
I'm just mad.
Then keep running.
그럼 계속 뛰어
You win!
또 졌다
-What did you have?
-Nothing beats...
네 건 뭔데?
상관없어, 제일 센 패가...
a three and a six.
3하고 6이걸랑
That, my friend, is "D Cup."
그게 이른바 'D컵'이지
How much have you won so far?
그럼 이제 얼마나 땄어?
이런, 700이다
-700.
-Not 700 exactly?
- 정확히 700은 아니지?
- 맞아
Double it.
따블이야
뭐?
In Cups, once you get $700,
you have to double it.
컵스에선 700달러 잃으면
따블로 쓰는 거야
- 진짜?
- 규칙은 내가 만든 게 아냐
I didn't make up the rules.
따블 보너스를 받고 나면
카드 한 장이 더 나가
Now, after you receive the doubling
bonus, you get one card.
That one card could be worth $100,
which brings your total to $1500.
운 좋으면 100달러짜리지
그럼 합이 1,500이야
Don't get excited, that won't happen
unless you get the.. No way!
너무 좋아하지 마
그런 일은 좀처럼... 미치겠네
이게 마지막 옷상자야
여기다 이렇게 써놓을게
This is the last box of your clothes.
I'm just gonna label it
"What were you thinking?"
'취향도 별나셔'
재미있네, 난 챈들러한테
그 말을 써놓으려고 했는데
I was just gonna go across
the hall and write that on Chandler.
얘들아, 상황을
악화시키긴 싫지만
Guys, I don't wanna make
things worse, but...
I don't wanna live with
Rachel anymore.
난 이제 레이첼이랑 못 살겠다
- 뭐?
You're so mean to each other.
너희들 정말 너무한다
나도 레이첼이랑 이렇게
끝내긴 싫어, 난 너 좋아해
I don't wanna end up like that
with Rachel. I still like you.
That's fine because I'm not moving.
피비, 괜찮아
난 이사 안 가니까
잠깐, 피비
얘 꼭 데려가
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
내가 악담을 좀 했지만 레이첼도
룸메이트로서 좋은 점이 있거든
I said some bad stuff...
but Rachel has qualities
that make her a good roommate.
Like what, Monica?
예를 들어 어떤 건데?
She has 147,000 pair of boots.
부츠가 14만 7천 켤레에다...
시작은 좋다
Good start, Mon.
너한테 빌려줄 수도 있어
She lets you borrow them.
그래, 너처럼 왕발로
늘여놓지만 않으면
And you stretch them out
with your big old clown feet.
Do you wanna live outside?
Because it's getting cold!
날도 추워지는데
길에서 벌벌 떨어볼래?
She gets tons of catalogs and folds
down the pages of things I'd like.
카탈로그도 엄청 많아
내가 좋아할 만한 건
접어서 표시해주거든
다른 건?
What else?
When I take a shower...
샤워하러 들어가 보면
she leaves me notes on the mirror.
거울에 뭐라고 써두곤 해
맞아, 내가 좀 그래
I do. I do do that.
That's nice. I like having things
to read in the bathroom.
그건 좋네
화장실에 읽을거리가
있으면 뿌듯하지
When I fall asleep on the couch...
내가 소파에서
책 읽다 잠들면...
she covers me with a blanket.
담요를 덮어 줘
그거야 뭐...
Well, you know,
I don't want you to be cold.
감기 걸리면 안 되잖아
그리고 내가 챈들러랑
같이 살겠다고 말했을 때
And when I told her I was gonna
move in with Chandler...
she was really supportive.
적극적으로 밀어줬어
You were so great.
이런 애가 어디 있니
큰 신세를 진 거야
You made it so easy.
And now you have to leave.
근데 이제 넌 떠나고...
And I have to live with a boy!
난 남자랑 살아야 돼!
괜찮을 거야
It's gonna be fine.
레이첼, 이젠 빨리
너랑 살고 싶다
Now I can't wait to live with you!
You know what we should do?
이럼 어떨까?
Bring Monica, and we'll live together!
We'll have so much fun!
모니카도 데려가서 셋이
같이 살면 진짜 신날 거야!
I think she's moving in with Chandler.
하지만 얘는
챈들러랑 살 텐데?
그렇구나
Oh, that's right.
You're still set on that?
아직도 그러고 싶어?
Kind of.
그래
뭐야?
Oh, my God!
세상에!
여보세요?
안녕, 모니카
짐 싸는 건 잘돼가?
How's the packing going?
Ben? He's fine. He's right..
Oh, my God!
벤이야 잘 있지
바로 옆에... 엄마야!
괜찮니?
Get your head out of your shirt
there, son!
셔츠에서 머리를 빼내렴
뭐?
Yeah, it's a pumpkin. I'll come pack.
맞아, 호박이야
가서 짐 쌀게
야
-What's wrong?
-Ross and I were helping pack...
왜 그래?
로스랑 짐 싸는 거 돕다
잠깐 쉬었는데
took a little break.
I lost $1500 to him in Cups!
컵스 때문에
1,500달러 잃었다
뭐야? 컵스에서
지다니 말도 안 돼
How did you lose at Cups?
너랑 똑같은 식으로
The same way you lost!
I started out with the king and the
queen. Bam! Ross gets a 2 and a 3.
킹이랑 퀸을 잡았는데, 꽝!
로스한텐 2랑 3이 있었어
Then I get a jack and a king.
Boom! Ross gets a 4 and 5.
잭과 킹을 잡았더니, 꿍!
로스 녀석은 4랑 5야
Even Ross was getting the Cup card,
the D Cup...
로스가 컵 카드, D컵
곱빼기 따따블 해먹는 동안
the sitting-down bonus. I didn't
even get half a cup! Nothing!
난 반 컵도 없어, 개털이야!
Oh, man!
미치겠다
걔도 처음 해봤대, 아무래도
컵스는 초짜 끗발이 무서워
He never played before either.
I think beginner's luck
is very important in Cups!
그럼 우리 한 판만 더하자
Let's play one more hand.
One more hand.
싫어, 더는 잃고 싶지 않아
이번엔 진심이야
No more! I cannot lose another dime.
I'm serious this time.
In fact, look.
사실 너한테 주고 싶은 게 있어
I wanna give you something.
Let me give it to you before
I pawn it for Cups money.
컵스로 다 날리기 전에
받아가라고
자, 이 녀석을 너한테 줄게
I want you to have
the big, white dog...
함께 지낸 시간을
기념하는 뜻이야
as a thank-you for being
such a great roommate.
어떻게 이걸 받나
네가 아끼는 거잖아
I can't take the big white dog.
You love it.
It's "him." Not "it."
'이거'가 아니라
'이 녀석'이야
What if I bought it from you?
그럼 내가 이걸 사면 어떨까
Then your nice gesture would be
giving it to me at a reasonable price.
그 마음이 너무 고마워서
후하게 쳐줄게, 1,500달러?
Say $1500?
잠깐, 이제야 감이 온다
Wait a second.
I see what you're trying to do here.
You're trying to give me money again!
또 나한테 돈을 주려는 거지?
When did I try to give you money?
또라니 언제 그랬는데?
아까 저기서 고지서 볼 때
Over there with the bills!
동정 받는 건 싫다고 했더니
너도 동의했잖아
You tried to give me charity,
I said no, you dropped it.
그 뒤로는 즐겁게 보냈지
We had a nice last night together.
We had some fun, we gambled, nobody
tried to give anybody any money.
신나게 도박도 하면서
돈을 주려는 시도는 없었어
Now you start with the
charity thing again!
그런데 또 갑자기
동정을 시작하잖아
도와주려는 거야
네가 걱정돼서 그래
I'm trying to help you out.
I wanna make sure that you're okay.
난 괜찮아
야, 챈들러
I will be okay.
You gotta get it out of your head
that I can't take care of myself.
날 앞가림도 못하는
어린애로 생각하지 마
난 돈 대주는 널
그리워하진 않아
I'm not gonna miss you helping me
out with money.
The only thing I'm gonna miss...
그리워질 게 있다면
그건 바로 너야
is you.
이 개도
And now the dog.
-Call me when you get there, okay?
-Okay.
- 도착하면 전화해
- 알았어
정말 보고 싶을 거야
I'm really gonna miss you.
참, 열쇠 돌려줘야지
I have your key.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
여기 있어
- 고마워
- 그래
God, this is silly.
I'll see you in a couple of hours.
정말 웃긴다
몇 시간 후면 또 볼 텐데
Bye, house.
안녕, 내 집아
- 안녕
- 잘 가
뭐해?
-She really left.
-I know.
정말로 가버렸어
그래
-Thank you.
-No problem, roomie.
고마워
천만에, 룸메이트
-Can I ask you a question?
-Sure.
- 뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 물론이지
저 개가 대체 왜 여기 있지?
What the hell is that dog doing here?
I invented the game of Cups
as a way to give Joey money.
조이한테 돈을 주려고
컵스 게임을 만든 거야
그래서 돈을 돌려달라?
-And now you want that money back?
-Exactly.
맞아
챈들러, 내가 푼수로 보이냐?
What kind of idiot do you
take me for?
It's not a real game.
I made it up.
진짜 게임이 아냐
내가 만든 거라고
네가 잃은 건 안됐지만
난 정당한 방법으로 땄어
I'm sorry you lost your money.
But I won it fair and square.
가짜 게임에서?!
At a fake game!
If you wanna try to
make some of it back...
돈을 되찾고 싶다면
기꺼이 상대해주지
I'd be glad to play you for it.
But I should warn you.
하지만 경고하는데
난 컵스의 도사거든
I am very good at Cups.
좋아, 지난번에 할 때
소서카드도 나왔겠지?
I assume the saucer card
came up when you played last.
아니
흠! 이번엔 나오나 볼까?
Let's see if it comes up this time.